'use strict';

const STORE = [
    {
        number: 1,
        question: "So, What is casper network?",
        options: [
            "The Casper Network is a layer two Proof-of-Stake blockchain",
            "The Casper Network is a layer one Proof-of-Work blockchain",
            "The Casper Network is a layer two Proof-of-Work blockchain",
            "The Casper Network is a layer one Proof-of-Stake blockchain",
        ],
        answer: "The Casper Network is a layer one Proof-of-Stake blockchain",
        explanation: "The Casper Network is a layer one Proof-of-Stake blockchain, the first provably live and safe version of CBC Casper, that is designed for real-world applications without sacrificing usability, decentralization, security, or scalability. Casper’s mission is to bring blockchain into the mainstream and create more open and transparent networks powered by the builders.",
    },
    {
        number: 2,
        question: "When did the Casper Network mainnet launch?",
        options: [
            "March 31,2021",
            "March 25,2021",
            "March 25,2020",
            "None of the above",
        ],
        answer: "March 31,2021",
        explanation: "The Mainnet launched March 31, 2021. Ref: Docs --> More about",
    },
    {   
        number: 3,
        question: "Casper in Which Terms?",
        options: [
            "Economic",
            "Non-Economic",
            "Both",
            "None of the above",
        ],
        answer: "Non-Economic",
        explanation: "Casper is an eventually-consistent blockchain-based consensus protocol. It favours availability over consistency, see the CAP theorem. It is always available, and consistent whenever possible. It is robust to unpredictable message delivery times because nodes come to consensus via re-organization of transactions, after delayed messages are eventually received.",
    },
    {   
        number: 4,
        question: "Who is faster for a validator to validate a block and bet on a block?",
        options: [
            "Proof-of-Stake",
            "Proof-of-Work",
            "Proof-of-Trust",
            "All of the above",
        ],
        answer: "Proof-of-Stake",
        explanation: "PoS is faster for a validator to validate a block and bet on a block comparing to PoW (Proof of Work) which solve a cryptographic puzzle in order to append the block in the blockchain. If PoS is faster then the whole blockchain will become faster and more scalable. This casper update can make Ethereum ready for the world wide adoption.",
    },
    {
        number: 5,
        question: "What are the proporties of Casper Network protocol?",
        options: [
            "Anyone can participate",
            "Consensus can be reached in a timely manner",
            "It quickly converges on an irreversible consensu",
            "All the Above",
        ],
        answer: "All the Above",
        explanation: "Please Refer to the Docs",
    },
    {
        number: 6,
        question: "Casper is the implementation that will eventually convert which chain into a Proof of Stake (PoS) blockchain ",
        options: [
            "Ethereum",
            "Polygon",
            "Solana",
            "Bitcoin",
        ],
        answer: "Ethereum",
        explanation: "Casper is the implementation that will eventually convert Ethereum into a Proof of Stake (PoS) blockchain (also known as Ethereum 2.0).",
    },
    {   
        number: 7,
        question: "How much Attacts of possibilities can still discussing by the CASPER developer?",
        options: [
            "30%",
            "10%",
            "91%",
            "51%",
        ],
        answer: "51%",
        explanation: "The penalty for cheating the rules is a validator’s stake (in ETH), meaning that network transgressions will be very expensive. However, developers are still discussing the possibilities of 51% attacks.",
    },
    {   
        number: 8,
        question: "What are the limitation of Casper Network?",
        options: [
            "its efficiency and security are still unproven",
            "Casper won’t be able to finalize blocks if Ethereum’s validating system becomes corrupted. ",
            "Only 2nd Option",
            "Both",
        ],
        answer: "Both",
        explanation: "Please Refer to the Docs",
    },
    {   
        number: 9,
        question: "Casper is what type of Network?",
        options: [
            "Permissionless",
            "Public blockchain",
            "Decentralized",
            "All the Above",
        ],
        answer: "All the Above",
        explanation: "Please Refer to the Docs",
    },
    {   
        number: 10,
        question: "What is CSPR?",
        options: [
            "Another Blockchain",
            "A Company",
            "Centralized Blockchain",
            "Native token on the Casper Network",
        ],
        answer: "Native token on the Casper Network",
        explanation: "Please Refer to the Docs",
    },

];